< JUSTIN MURRAH >

116 Wilson Dam Avenue Sheffield, AL 35660 470.609.0699

justin.murrah.dev@gmail.com https://github.com/Jaymoo87

As a budding software developer, my mission is to apply my coding expertise and creative problem-solving skills to build cutting-edge software that wows users. With an insatiable thirst for knowledge and a passion for teamwork, I'm committed to honing my craft alongside seasoned developers, while contributing to projects that push the limits of what's possible. Whether it's front-end or back-end development, I'm always up for a challenge, and I'm driven to deliver top-notch code that makes a real impact.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Business and Team Development Consultant

Rick's Farm Market September 2020 - October 2022

Developed new branch of small business. Researched, developed, and implemented new ways to improve business and service processes. Created complex databases to inventory supplies, deliveries, and perishables.

Mentored new and established employees.

Executive Chef

Red Clay Table September 2018 - March 2020

Built a highly effective team that was able to excel in a high volume, high intensity environment. Developed and implemented business practices that provided ideal customer experience.

Head Chef

Chapel Hills Country Club November 2015 - July 2018

Managed a large team by corporate standards with a high level of attention to detail, organization, and customer service.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp Covalence.io - Birmingham, AL 2022

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and GIS

University of North Alabama 2005 - 2008 Completed 3 years of study towards degree

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

- javaScript, HTML5, CSS, jQuery, MySQL, Postgres, React, MongoDB, Vite, AWS, Next.js, Typescript, Tailwind, Bootstrap, Node.js, Express, Git, GitHub, MaterialUI, Heroku
- Teamwork, multitasking, attention to detail, leadership and team management
- Software and web development
- Database normalization

</SOFTWARE ENGINEER>